{"Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`EU`, `rejects`, `German`, `call`, `to`, `boycott`, `British`, `lamb`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [3, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "predicted": [3, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 6, 7, 0], "metric": [0.4, 0.3666666666666667, 0.38181818181818183]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Only`, `France`, `and`, `Britain`, `backed`, `Fischler`, `'s`, `proposal`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 5, 0, 5, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 5, 0, 5, 0, 1, 8, 0, 0], "metric": [0.75, 0.7083333333333334, 0.7272727272727273]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`It`, `brought`, `in`, `4,275`, `tonnes`, `of`, `British`, `mutton`, `,`, `some`, `10`, `percent`, `of`, `overall`, `imports`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 7, 0, 0, 8, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [0.25, 0.21666666666666667, 0.23214285714285715]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Rare`, `Hendrix`, `song`, `draft`, `sells`, `for`, `almost`, `$`, `17,000`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 8, 0], "metric": [0.5, 0.4444444444444444, 0.46875]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`A`, `rare`, `early`, `handwritten`, `draft`, `of`, `a`, `song`, `by`, `U.S.`, `guitar`, `legend`, `Jimi`, `Hendrix`, `was`, `sold`, `for`, `almost`, `$`, `17,000`, `on`, `Thursday`, `at`, `an`, `auction`, `of`, `some`, `of`, `the`, `late`, `musician`, `'s`, `favourite`, `possessions`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 7, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 8, 3, 4, 6, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1], "metric": [0.3888888888888889, 0.4236111111111111, 0.3959131545338442]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`They`, `included`, `a`, `black`, `lacquer`, `and`, `mother`, `of`, `pearl`, `inlaid`, `box`, `used`, `by`, `Hendrix`, `to`, `store`, `his`, `drugs`, `,`, `which`, `an`, `anonymous`, `Australian`, `purchaser`, `bought`, `for`, `5,060`, `pounds`, `(`, `$`, `7,845`, `)`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 2, 0, 0, 6, 7, 8, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [0.2222222222222222, 0.2007168458781362, 0.21031746031746032]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`The`, `guitarist`, `died`, `of`, `a`, `drugs`, `overdose`, `in`, `1970`, `aged`, `27`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 8, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [0.25, 0.1875, 0.21428571428571427]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`BEIJING`, `1996-08-22`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5, 0], "predicted": [5, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`China`, `says`, `time`, `right`, `for`, `Taiwan`, `talks`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0], "predicted": [5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`German`, `July`, `car`, `registrations`, `up`, `14.2`, `pct`, `yr`, `/`, `yr`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [7, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [5, 0, 7, 8, 0, 0, 7, 7, 0, 7, 0], "metric": [0.25, 0.125, 0.16666666666666666]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Motor-bike`, `registration`, `rose`, `32.7`, `percent`, `in`, `the`, `period`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0], "metric": [0.5, 0.4444444444444444, 0.47058823529411764]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Volkswagen`, `AG`, `won`, `77,719`, `registrations`, `,`, `slightly`, `more`, `than`, `a`, `quarter`, `of`, `the`, `total`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Opel`, `AG`, `together`, `with`, `General`, `Motors`, `came`, `in`, `second`, `place`, `with`, `49,269`, `registrations`, `,`, `16.4`, `percent`, `of`, `the`, `overall`, `figure`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [3, 4, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [3, 4, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 8, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [0.42857142857142855, 0.2689075630252101, 0.32440476190476186]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Third`, `was`, `Ford`, `with`, `35,563`, `registrations`, `,`, `or`, `11.7`, `percent`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Only`, `Seat`, `and`, `Porsche`, `had`, `fewer`, `registrations`, `in`, `July`, `1996`, `compared`, `to`, `last`, `year`, `'s`, `July`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 3, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 3, 4, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 7, 0, 0, 0, 6, 8, 5, 0], "metric": [0.2857142857142857, 0.2285714285714286, 0.25]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Porsche`, `'s`, `registrations`, `fell`, `to`, `554`, `from`, `643`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`ATHENS`, `1996-08-22`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5, 0], "predicted": [5, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`BayerVB`, `sets`, `C$`, `100`, `million`, `six-year`, `bond`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [3, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [3, 0, 7, 0, 8, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [0.75, 0.7083333333333334, 0.7272727272727273]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`LONDON`, `1996-08-22`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5, 0], "predicted": [5, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`The`, `following`, `bond`, `was`, `announced`, `by`, `lead`, `manager`, `Toronto`, `Dominion`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 5, 4, 0], "metric": [0.16666666666666666, 0.14814814814814814, 0.1568627450980392]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`BORROWER`, `BAYERISCHE`, `VEREINSBANK`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 3, 4], "predicted": [0, 3, 4], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`AMT`, `C$`, `100`, `MLN`, `COUPON`, `6.625`, `MATURITY`, `24.SEP.02`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [7, 0, 8, 0, 7, 8, 0, 5], "metric": [0.16666666666666666, 0.07142857142857142, 0.1]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`TYPE`, `STRAIGHT`, `ISS`, `PRICE`, `100.92`, `PAY`, `DATE`, `24.SEP.96`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 3, 7, 8, 7, 5, 6], "metric": [0.16666666666666666, 0.041666666666666664, 0.06666666666666667]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`FULL`, `FEES`, `1.875`, `REOFFER`, `99.32`, `SPREAD`, `+20`, `BP`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 8], "metric": [0.3333333333333333, 0.25, 0.2857142857142857]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`MOODY`, `AA1`, `LISTING`, `LUX`, `PAY`, `FREQ`, `=`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [1, 0, 0, 7, 7, 8, 0], "metric": [0.25, 0.10714285714285714, 0.15]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`S&P`, `=`, `DENOMS`, `(`, `K`, `)`, `1-10-100`, `SALE`, `LIMITS`, `US`, `/`, `UK`, `/`, `CA`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 5, 0, 5], "predicted": [3, 0, 7, 0, 8, 0, 0, 8, 4, 5, 0, 5, 0, 5], "metric": [0.5, 0.43333333333333335, 0.4583333333333333]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`NEG`, `PLG`, `NO`, `CRS`, `DEFLT`, `NO`, `FORCE`, `MAJ`, `=`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0], "metric": [0.5, 0.4444444444444444, 0.47058823529411764]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`GOV`, `LAW`, `GERMAN`, `HOME`, `CTRY`, `=`, `TAX`, `PROVS`, `STANDARD`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 7], "metric": [0.25, 0.1875, 0.21428571428571427]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`MGT`, `/`, `UND`, `0.275`, `SELL`, `CONC`, `1.60`, `PRAECIP`, `=`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 8, 0, 8, 0], "metric": [0.3333333333333333, 0.2222222222222222, 0.26666666666666666]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`UNDERLYING`, `GOVT`, `BOND`, `7.0`, `PCT`, `SEPT`, `2001`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 3, 4, 0, 7, 5, 6], "metric": [0.16666666666666666, 0.047619047619047616, 0.07407407407407407]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`NOTES`, `BAYERISCHE`, `VEREINSBANK`, `IS`, `JOINT`, `LEAD`, `MANAGER`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 3, 4, 0, 7, 8, 1], "metric": [0.5, 0.39999999999999997, 0.42857142857142855]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`--`, `London`, `Newsroom`, `+44`, `171`, `542`, `7658`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 5, 3, 7, 8, 8, 6], "metric": [0.14285714285714285, 0.028571428571428574, 0.047619047619047616]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Venantius`, `sets`, `$`, `300`, `million`, `January`, `1999`, `FRN`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [1, 0, 7, 8, 4, 5, 6, 3, 0], "metric": [0.125, 0.03125, 0.05]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`BORROWER`, `VENANTIUS`, `AB`, `(`, `SWEDISH`, `NATIONAL`, `MORTGAGE`, `AGENCY`, `)`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 3, 4, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 1, 3, 0, 5, 6, 4, 8, 0], "metric": [0.125, 0.0625, 0.08333333333333333]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`AMT`, `$`, `300`, `MLN`, `SPREAD`, `-`, `12.5`, `BP`, `MATURITY`, `21.JAN.99`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 7, 8, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "metric": [0.3333333333333333, 0.2333333333333333, 0.2745098039215686]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`TYPE`, `FRN`, `BASE`, `3M`, `LIBOR`, `PAY`, `DATE`, `S23.SEP.96`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [7, 0, 0, 3, 8, 0, 5, 6], "metric": [0.3333333333333333, 0.2380952380952381, 0.26666666666666666]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`LAST`, `S&P`, `AA+`, `REOFFER`, `=`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 3, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 7, 8, 8, 0], "metric": [0.25, 0.125, 0.16666666666666666]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`NOTES`, `S`, `SHORT`, `FIRST`, `COUPON`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`LISTING`, `LONDON`, `DENOMS`, `(`, `K`, `)`, `1-10-100`, `SALE`, `LIMITS`, `US`, `/`, `UK`, `/`, `JP`, `/`, `FR`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 5, 0, 5, 0, 5], "predicted": [0, 5, 0, 0, 7, 0, 8, 0, 0, 5, 0, 5, 0, 5, 0, 5], "metric": [0.5, 0.4545454545454546, 0.475]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`NEG`, `PLG`, `YES`, `CRS`, `DEFLT`, `NO`, `FORCE`, `MAJ`, `IPMA`, `2`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 8, 0], "metric": [0.3333333333333333, 0.26666666666666666, 0.2962962962962963]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`MGT`, `/`, `UND`, `5`, `BP`, `SELL`, `CONC`, `5`, `BP`, `PRAECIP`, `=`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [7, 0, 8, 5, 3, 4, 8, 6, 7, 1, 0], "metric": [0.125, 0.022727272727272728, 0.038461538461538464]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`NOTES`, `ISSUED`, `OFF`, `EMTN`, `PROGRAMME`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 3, 4], "metric": [0.3333333333333333, 0.19999999999999998, 0.25]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Port`, `conditions`, `update`, `-`, `Syria`, `-`, `Lloyds`, `Shipping`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 3, 4, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 3, 4, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Port`, `conditions`, `from`, `Lloyds`, `Shipping`, `Intelligence`, `Service`, `--`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Israel`, `plays`, `down`, `fears`, `of`, `war`, `with`, `Syria`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0], "predicted": [5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Colleen`, `Siegel`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [1, 2], "predicted": [1, 2], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Rabinovich`, `is`, `winding`, `up`, `his`, `term`, `as`, `ambassador`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [1, 0, 0, 0, 8, 4, 0, 7, 0], "metric": [0.4, 0.325, 0.3538461538461538]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`He`, `will`, `be`, `replaced`, `by`, `Eliahu`, `Ben-Elissar`, `,`, `a`, `former`, `Israeli`, `envoy`, `to`, `Egypt`, `and`, `right-wing`, `Likud`, `party`, `politician`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 5, 0, 7, 3, 4, 8, 0], "metric": [0.5, 0.5916666666666667, 0.5224358974358975]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Syria`, `accused`, `Israel`, `on`, `Wednesday`, `of`, `launching`, `a`, `hysterical`, `campaign`, `against`, `it`, `after`, `Israeli`, `television`, `reported`, `that`, `Damascus`, `had`, `recently`, `test`, `fired`, `a`, `missile`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [5, 0, 3, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 6, 4, 8, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [0.20634920634920634, 0.16326530612244897, 0.18168498168498168]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Peace`, `talks`, `between`, `the`, `two`, `sides`, `were`, `last`, `held`, `in`, `February`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 7, 0], "metric": [0.3333333333333333, 0.2777777777777778, 0.30303030303030304]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`are`, `full`, `of`, `expressions`, `and`, `declarations`, `that`, `must`, `be`, `worrying`, `...`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7], "metric": [0.5, 0.45454545454545453, 0.47619047619047616]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Israel`, `'s`, `Channel`, `Two`, `television`, `said`, `Damascus`, `had`, `sent`, `a`, `\"`, `calming`, `signal`, `\"`, `to`, `Israel`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0], "predicted": [5, 0, 3, 4, 7, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 8, 6, 8, 9, 0, 5, 0], "metric": [0.5, 0.4479166666666667, 0.46710526315789475]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`It`, `gave`, `no`, `source`, `for`, `the`, `report`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Netanyahu`, `and`, `Levy`, `'s`, `spokesmen`, `said`, `they`, `could`, `not`, `confirm`, `it`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [1, 0, 1, 8, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [0.5, 0.45, 0.4722222222222222]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`TUNIS`, `1996-08-22`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5, 0], "predicted": [5, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`\"`, `This`, `is`, `not`, `true`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Iraqi`, `Kurdish`, `areas`, `bordering`, `Iran`, `are`, `under`, `the`, `control`, `of`, `guerrillas`, `of`, `the`, `Iraqi`, `Kurdish`, `Patriotic`, `Union`, `of`, `Kurdistan`, `(`, `PUK`, `)`, `group`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [7, 8, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [5, 3, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 4, 7, 8, 0, 6, 0, 0, 7, 0, 3], "metric": [0.3129251700680272, 0.29387755102040813, 0.24149659863945577]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Clashes`, `between`, `the`, `two`, `parties`, `broke`, `out`, `at`, `the`, `weekend`, `in`, `the`, `most`, `serious`, `fighting`, `since`, `a`, `U.S.-sponsored`, `ceasefire`, `last`, `year`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 6, 8, 7, 0, 3, 4, 1, 2, 6, 8], "metric": [0.1111111111111111, 0.06349206349206349, 0.08080808080808081]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`It`, `said`, `about`, `100`, `Iraqi`, `Kurds`, `were`, `killed`, `or`, `wounded`, `in`, `the`, `attack`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 8, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [0.2, 0.2, 0.2]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`A`, `U.S.-led`, `air`, `force`, `in`, `southern`, `Turkey`, `protects`, `Iraqi`, `Kurds`, `from`, `possible`, `attacks`, `by`, `Baghdad`, `troops`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 7, 8, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 6, 3, 0, 1, 2, 0, 8, 0, 7, 4, 0, 0], "metric": [0.1111111111111111, 0.08333333333333333, 0.09523809523809523]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`MANAMA`, `1996-08-22`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5, 0], "predicted": [5, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`The`, `spot`, `riyal`, `was`, `put`, `at`, `3.7504`, `/`, `06`, `to`, `the`, `dollar`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 8, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0], "metric": [0.25, 0.19230769230769232, 0.21739130434782608]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`JERUSALEM`, `1996-08-22`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5, 0], "predicted": [5, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Abu`, `Rdainah`, `said`, `Arafat`, `had`, `decided`, `against`, `flying`, `to`, `the`, `West`, `Bank`, `on`, `Thursday`, `,`, `after`, `Israel`, `lifted`, `the`, `ban`, `,`, `because`, `he`, `had`, `a`, `busy`, `schedule`, `in`, `Gaza`, `and`, `would`, `not`, `be`, `free`, `until`, `Monday`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [1, 2, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [1, 2, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 8, 0, 4, 0, 2, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 6, 0, 0], "metric": [0.3472222222222222, 0.4555555555555555, 0.3761316872427984]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Hilary`, `Gush`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [1, 2], "predicted": [1, 2], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`DUBAI`, `1996-08-22`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5, 0], "predicted": [5, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`There`, `is`, `no`, `objection`, `to`, `their`, `travel`, `,`, `\"`, `he`, `added`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 1, 0, 0], "metric": [0.3333333333333333, 0.2777777777777778, 0.30303030303030304]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`It`, `has`, `since`, `been`, `silent`, `on`, `the`, `issue`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`He`, `did`, `not`, `elaborate`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [1, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [0.5, 0.4, 0.4444444444444444]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Taleban`, `said`, `its`, `shipment`, `of`, `ammunition`, `from`, `Albania`, `was`, `evidence`, `of`, `Russian`, `military`, `support`, `for`, `Rabbani`, `'s`, `government`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [7, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 6, 4, 8, 0, 1, 2, 8, 0], "metric": [0.3333333333333333, 0.3037037037037037, 0.3162393162393162]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Moscow`, `said`, `the`, `crew`, `'s`, `nationality`, `was`, `coincidental`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [5, 0, 0, 0, 7, 8, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [0.5, 0.4375, 0.4642857142857143]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Numerous`, `diplomatic`, `attempts`, `to`, `free`, `the`, `seven`, `failed`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`PRESS`, `DIGEST`, `-`, `Iraq`, `-`, `Aug`, `22`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 7, 0, 0], "metric": [0.6666666666666666, 0.6190476190476191, 0.6410256410256411]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`BAGHDAD`, `1996-08-22`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5, 0], "predicted": [5, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`THAWRA`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [3], "predicted": [0], "metric": [0.0, 0.0, 0.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`-`, `Iraq`, `'s`, `President`, `Saddam`, `Hussein`, `meets`, `with`, `chairman`, `of`, `the`, `Russian`, `liberal`, `democratic`, `party`, `Vladimir`, `Zhirinovsky`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 5, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0], "predicted": [0, 5, 6, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 7, 8, 8, 8, 1, 2, 0], "metric": [0.5555555555555556, 0.49074074074074076, 0.5098039215686274]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`IRAQ`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5], "predicted": [5], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`PRESS`, `DIGEST`, `-`, `Lebanon`, `-`, `Aug`, `22`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 7, 2, 0], "metric": [0.5, 0.4285714285714286, 0.45833333333333337]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`BEIRUT`, `1996-08-22`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5, 0], "predicted": [5, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Reuters`, `has`, `not`, `verified`, `these`, `stories`, `and`, `does`, `not`, `vouch`, `for`, `their`, `accuracy`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`-`, `Prime`, `Minister`, `Hariri`, `:`, `Israeli`, `threats`, `do`, `no`, `serve`, `peace`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 3, 4, 1, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0], "metric": [0.3333333333333333, 0.2833333333333333, 0.30392156862745096]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`The`, `three`, `main`, `lists`, `have`, `been`, `prepared`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`AL-ANWAR`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [3], "predicted": [3], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`-`, `Continued`, `criticism`, `of`, `law`, `violation`, `incidents`, `--`, `which`, `occurred`, `in`, `the`, `Mount`, `Lebanon`, `elections`, `last`, `Sunday`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 3, 4, 7, 1, 0], "metric": [0.14285714285714285, 0.10714285714285714, 0.12244897959183673]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`-`, `Financial`, `negotiations`, `between`, `Lebanon`, `and`, `Pakistan`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 5, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 5, 0, 3, 0, 4, 6], "metric": [0.2, 0.13333333333333333, 0.16]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`NIDA'A`, `AL-WATAN`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [3, 4], "predicted": [7, 4], "metric": [0.3333333333333333, 0.3333333333333333, 0.3333333333333333]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`CME`, `live`, `and`, `feeder`, `cattle`, `calls`, `range`, `mixed`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`The`, `continued`, `strong`, `tone`, `to`, `cash`, `cattle`, `and`, `beef`, `markets`, `should`, `prompt`, `further`, `support`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [0.5, 0.4666666666666667, 0.4827586206896552]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`MONTGOMERY`, `,`, `Ala`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5, 0, 5, 0], "predicted": [5, 0, 6, 0], "metric": [0.6666666666666666, 0.5, 0.5555555555555555]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`1996-08-22`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0], "predicted": [0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`The`, `notes`, `were`, `bought`, `for`, `$`, `31.5`, `million`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 8, 8, 0], "metric": [0.3333333333333333, 0.2222222222222222, 0.26666666666666666]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`RESEARCH`, `ALERT`, `-`, `Lehman`, `starts`, `SNET`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 3, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 3, 0], "metric": [0.6666666666666666, 0.5, 0.5555555555555555]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`--`, `The`, `analyst`, `also`, `set`, `an`, `earnings`, `estimate`, `for`, `the`, `1997`, `year`, `,`, `but`, `the`, `figure`, `was`, `not`, `immediately`, `available`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 7, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [0.3333333333333333, 0.30158730158730157, 0.31666666666666665]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`--`, `Southern`, `New`, `England`, `closed`, `at`, `38-1/2`, `Wednesday`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 5, 6, 2, 0, 0, 7, 1, 0], "metric": [0.125, 0.08333333333333333, 0.1]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`PHOENIX`, `1996-08-22`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [5, 0], "predicted": [5, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Jul`, `31`, `,`, `Jul`, `31`, `,`, `Jul`, `31`, `,`, `Jul`, `31`, `,`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`1996`, `1995`, `1996`, `1995`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Income`, `Statement`, `Data`, `:`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [7, 8, 8, 0], "metric": [0.3333333333333333, 0.08333333333333333, 0.13333333333333333]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Software`, `Revenue`, `2,383`, `1,558`, `1,086`, `1,074`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 7, 8, 8, 8, 8], "metric": [0.3333333333333333, 0.05555555555555555, 0.09523809523809523]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Services`, `Revenue`, `1,154`, `692`, `624`, `465`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Operating`, `Income`, `906`, `962`, `599`, `515`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Net`, `Income`, `821`, `512`, `565`, `301`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Earnings`, `Per`, `Share`, `0.31`, `0.34`, `0.19`, `0.20`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Jul`, `31`, `,`, `1996`, `Jan`, `31`, `,`, `1996`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 5, 7, 8, 0, 5], "metric": [0.25, 0.125, 0.16666666666666666]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Balance`, `Sheet`, `Data`, `:`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Total`, `Assets`, `14,196`, `7,138`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [1.0, 1.0, 1.0]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Greek`, `socialists`, `give`, `PM`, `green`, `light`, `for`, `election`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [7, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [5, 0, 0, 7, 8, 0, 0, 0, 0], "metric": [0.25, 0.1875, 0.21428571428571427]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`Prime`, `Minister`, `Costas`, `Simitis`, `will`, `make`, `an`, `official`, `announcement`, `after`, `a`, `cabinet`, `meeting`, `later`, `on`, `Thursday`, `,`, `said`, `Skandalidis`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0], "predicted": [0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 1, 0], "metric": [0.3333333333333333, 0.37745098039215685, 0.33888888888888885]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`PRESS`, `DIGEST`, `-`, `France`, `-`, `Le`, `Monde`, `Aug`, `22`, `.`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n    Example of the correct output:\n    {'ner_tags': [0, 0, 5, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0],\n    'tokens': ['SOCCER', '-', 'JAPAN', 'GET', 'LUCKY', 'WIN', ',', 'CHINA', 'IN', 'SURPRISE', 'DEFEAT', '.']}": {"correct": [0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0], "predicted": [0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 3, 4, 7, 8, 0], "metric": [0.6666666666666666, 0.6190476190476191, 0.638888888888889]}, "Identify each named entity from the following sequence of tokens and classify it by the NER tags. Each token is enquoted with \"`\" and \"`\" is not part of token:\n    - NER tags: {'O': 0, 'B-PER': 1, 'I-PER': 2, 'B-ORG': 3, 'I-ORG': 4, 'B-LOC': 5, 'I-LOC': 6, 'B-MISC': 7, 'I-MISC': 8}\n    Tokens: '`PARIS`, `1996-08-22`'\n    Return the response in JSON format with the fields: ner_tags, tokens.\n    Each token has to be evaluated. The number of tags must match the number of tokens of each token type. \n   